Oh?
Is Sentaro late again?
Looks like.
Window shopping?
Might as well.
Huh?
Oh yeah, the summer festival is tomorrow.
What time you goin'?
You guys meeting up somewhere?
Beats me.
What?
Dunno.
Didn't get in touch with her.
What? What do you mean?
Did something happen?
Not really...
It's just that I kinda have this feeling
that we're not gonna be dating.
S-Seriously?
Hey!
My bad, my bad. Did I keep ya waiting?
And... Huh? What's wrong?
Nothing really. I was just telling Kuwa
I might not go to the festival tomorrow.
What?! But you said you were
goin' with the Prince...
Sentaro!
Oh...
I'll treat ya to a caramel frap.
Huh? Oh, yeah. Thanks.
Then let's all go together!
To the festival!
I'd be happy to have you, Ichi!
When we're with you, Ichi,
lots of girls come talk to us!
Right. Forgot that's the
type of guy you are, Sentaro.
H-Heh, gonna go buy that frap!
Ichi, you sure you're okay with that?
Doesn't matter if I am.
There's nothing I can do about it, y'know.
If it's a no-go then I just go
back to the way things were.
I'm a frivolous guy, so I bounce back
from things like that.
Liar.
It was different with
Takiguchi-san, wasn't it?
You looked like you really
caught feelings there.
What's the hold up?!
Coming.
Is our promise still on?
Ichi!
The frap!
Coming!
Nobara-chan, did you do the next problem?
Oh, I just did it.
Let me see.
Do it yourself.
Hey.
What should we do about the summer festival tomorrow?
For meeting up and such
Wh
What
What time
Besides, I don't even know if it's right.
What time did
Oh, come on. It's fine.
Jeez.
Oh, so this is this, and that's...
What the?!
Did you have a system crash
from studying too hard?
Sorry, don't mind me.
You say that, but...
Huh? Is that the muffin
you made yesterday?
I thought you gave it to Senpai?
I couldn't give it to him.
Are you okay?
We have zero experience when
it comes to relationships,
so we might not be of much help.
But you can still talk to us about it.
Thanks.
But this is my problem, so it's
up to me to do something about it.
Still, if a time comes
when I do need help,
you guys will be the first I go to.
So, when the time comes,
please help me out.
Well, of course!
Give us all ya got!
Oh, but I wouldn't give
away that muffin now, okay?
It's summer after all.
Okay.
The distance between Senpai and
I is steadily closing.
But the closer we get,
the less we seem to click.
I want to do something about it,
but it never works out.
It's irritating.
Y'know,
I like you, Ichimura.
Huh? What's this? What's this?
Ichi, you're going out with Hasegawa?!
Since when?
Yesterday.
Are you serious?! Damn it!
I was going for Hasegawa!
Oh, my bad.
Too bad, Nakabayashi.
Ichi gets all the cute girls, man!
I don't think you should
go out with Hasegawa-san.
Yeah, her face is cute,
but she's been bragging about
you to girls from other schools.
Saying stuff like, "Don't you wish you
had a rich, handsome boyfriend like me?"
What, seriously? That's rude.
Yeah, unforgivable, isn't it?
Just kiddin'.
I already know all about that.
That's right!
He's seriously rich.
Part of the Ichimura group or whatever.
Is her tone normally like that?
Wha? His house seems dope.
I know, right?
That's sweet.
Really amazing.
Is there a pool in the yard?
I haven't gone over to his
place yet, so I don't know.
But the girls are all over him
because he's so handsome.
I feel like I snagged
the big prize, you know?
Wow, you're horrible!
They're talking about me like
I'm some kind of commodity.
Rich.
Handsome.
Prince.
Those three words define who I am...
She's been talking about what you might
get her for Christmas, too.
What? I dunno if we're gonna
be together till Christmas.
Seriously...
It really pisses me off that
she's taking advantage of you!
I'll listen to you vent if you want!
You can call me any time, okay?!
Wow, thanks.
Jeez, what bull.
You just want a rich,
handsome boyfriend, too.
Kohaku.
Ichimura-kun.
Ichi!
In the end, they're all the same.
What they want is the status
of dating the Prince.
That's why I never expected anything
and didn't ask for anything in return.
I'm not interested in
people to begin with.
It seems Ryu-kun broke
up with them, and...
He just needs to get
his priorities straight.
When it comes to love, just having
a taste of it should be enough.
No Smoking
Due to the
summer
festival,
vehicles
prohibited.
Under
Surveillance
Yoi!
Could you take this upstairs for me?
Okay!
Anyway, what's this about you wanting
to help out at work all of a sudden?
You're not going to the festival
with your friends this year?
What? No, they're both
busy this year, so...
I never heard back from Senpai.
And without any fanfare,
the day arrived.
I mean, I really should just contact him.
Nature's Blessing Rice
But...
What would I do if he
said, "Let's not go"?
I couldn't stop thinking about that,
so I just didn't say anything.
Yoi-san, I'll help with that.
Thank you very much.
Please place it on the shelf over there.
All right.
By the way, whatever happened with
that person you were talking about?
The one who wasn't sure whether to wear
a yukata to the summer festival or not.
Oh, uh...
She decided not to go.
What?! Why is that?
She's a coward.
She becomes especially timid
when it comes to him.
Not to mention, she doesn't really
know anything about falling in love.
And while she was trying to work it out,
it just slipped away from her...
Sort of.
But she felt that way because
she loves him, didn't she?
I mean, when you love someone,
you don't want to look uncool
or clumsy in front of them,
and you don't want to get hurt, right?
Besides, you know right
away if you love someone.
Because...
You'll always find them.
No matter how crowded a place may be,
you'll spot them right away.
Before you realize it,
you can't stop watching them.
And once you see them,
you can't tear your eyes away.
We often know ourselves the least.
Um!
Thank you very much!
Huh?
Dad! I'm leaving!
Sorry!
Huh? What?
Is she in a rebellious phase?
Hello? Kotobuki? Nobara?
What's up, Yoi-chan?
Are you outside? And running?
Yeah! Um...
Fortune Telling
I know it's awkward
to ask this now, but...
Do you happen to have a yukata?
What? Sorry, I don't.
Me neither.
Th-That's what I figured.
Sorry for suddenly asking
something weird.
Oh! A rental!
When I was writing a story about
dating in a kimono before,
I interviewed a nearby
kimono rental store.
I'll send you the link right now!
Nice, Nobara-chan!
It's closer than I thought.
Thanks, Nobara! You too, Kotobuki!
Festivals are awesome!
You're really enjoying
yourself, aren't you?
Of course I am!
There's still lots of places
to visit, so let's go!
Oh yeah?
Oh, hey!
It's Shun-kun and his crew!
Seriously, is it just you and
the guys? Hilarious.
Funny we ran into you.
Ugh.
What?! You're the girls
from Class D, right?
What are the odds?
Totally unlikely!
But I can't believe you came
after turning down our invite!
What? What's this about an invite?
What?! No way! You guys invited us?!
Yeah, we did.
Sorry, I figured you wouldn't want to go
with them, so I said we weren't going,
What? Thanks!
but it seems like the info got out.
Nah. It's nothin' you need
to apologize for, Kuwa.
But still, would it be bad if
Takiguchi-san found out about this?
Ah... Not really.
I invited her, but she didn't respond.
What, seriously?
How did you invite her?
Did you say something weird?
Not really. I just asked her...
if the promise was still...
I'm sorry. I have work today.
Okay, got it.
Is our promise still on?
I'm sorry. I have work today.
Okay, got it.
Is our promise still on?
I'm sorry. I have work today.
Okay, got it.
Is our promise still on?
I'm sorry. I have work today.
Okay, got it.
Is our promise still on?
Crap. I didn't send it.
You airhead!
And your battery is at two percent!
I thought I sent it!
So just send it now!
What are you guys talking about?
Hey, we should go, too.
Everyone's about to leave.
Sorry. Go on without me.
What am I doing?
I'm so dense.
And selfish as well.
I didn't want him to hate me.
I didn't want to be disappointed.
I was focused on my own pride,
and on protecting myself.
Is our promise still on?
But Senpai still...
always came to me regardless.
Damn it, why are they out of chargers?
Okay, got it.
Today
Is our promise still on?
I'm pretty sure there was a
convenience store across the way.
Oh!
There you are!
What are you doing by yourself?
Let's walk around and enjoy ourselves.
You don't have to worry about me.
Go play with the others.
What? But that no fun.
It'll be super fun. Don't worry.
Liar. You look super
bored right now, Ichimura.
I'm not.
I'm super...
She was a different kind of girl.
The line of her neck stands out,
maybe because of her short hair.
Manga Encyclopedia
She reminded me of something.
This had to be it.
She was a kind of girl
I've never met before, and...
No matter where we were, I was somehow
able to notice her right away.
I wonder if there's
a way I can have her...
Look this way.
Turn around.
Only have eyes for me!
Yoi-chan!
Huh? Damn it!
Huh? Hey!
Seriously, what's going on?
Yoi-chan!
Yoi!
You've come this far.
Don't run now.
But, you were with a girl, so...
I thought I'd be in the way.
Huh?
That's seriously ridiculous.
Rid—
Could you please spare me that crap?
It's not!
It's not... ridiculous.
To me...
I'm... far less honest than you think.
And I'm a pain to deal with.
Because...
The only time I've ever held hands
with a boy was during a folk dance.
Being told I had a sweet tooth,
being carried like a princess,
being called by my first name,
and being told I'm... cute...
I'd never had any of that before, and...
I've never met anyone who
was interested in me before.
So, when someone actually made
advances towards me,
I didn't want to be thought of
as someone easily won over.
I didn't want to be seen as someone
gullible and easily tricked.
Because...
I really do want you to
be more into me, Senpai!
I want you to say more sweet things to me!
In fact, I want you to be
completely infatuated with me!
I'm sorry for trying to
act like a good girl.
Yoi-chan...
Are you saying you love me?
Yes.
Look at me.
Take off your mask.
Take it off and look at me.
Damn. I could die right here.
Senpai's heart...
It's beating so fast.
Um...
You're going to get heatstroke.
Yep.
W-We have to go to the festival, too.
Someone might see...
Yeah... But...
It's still not enough.
Um...
No!
My... My heart isn't ready.
Well...
We can cross that bridge
when we come to it.
I'll wait patiently.
Thank you.
For now, let's enjoy the festival.
Yeah.
We gotta be careful that Kuwa
and Sentaro don't find us.
If we run into them now,
it'll be a pain to deal with.
Such a big hand.
Oh, yeah.
The yukata...
It looks great on you.
It makes me super happy.
Ever since we met...
Whenever I'm with Senpai,
I feel like I can just be a girl.
The boy who's special to me.
You on the Night of the Festival
Translation:
Timing:
Editing:
Quality Control:
Final Quality Control:
Yukari Murase-Louden
Andy Ellis
Gabriella Alabanza
Salem Alabanza
Elizabeth Ellis